You're telling me this actress person...
你泡过的马子里
...is the only woman you ever wanted who didn't want you back?
只有这个女演员没有反应？
Oh,my God.
天哪
Is this what it's like to be you?
这就是你的人生？
-You're crazy about her,huh? -You have no idea.
你真的很喜欢她？ 你有所不知
When we're on stage,I get to kiss her and touch her.
上了台，我可以吻她、摸她
She goes home with the director...
然后她跟导演回家
...and it's like somebody's ripping out my heart.
我就心如刀割
Oh,it's so great to see you feeling like this.
看你这样，感觉真好
Dad called this morning.
爸早上打电话来
Aunt Sylvia passed away.
施薇亚姑姑死了
We were all pretty shaken up about it.
我们都很震惊
Am I missing something?
我漏听了什么？
I thought death was supposed to be sad,in a way.
死亡不是悲伤的事吗？
Well,Aunt Sylvia was...
施薇亚姑姑…
... not a nice person.
不是一个好人
She was a cruel,cranky old bitch.
她是个残忍的糟老太婆
And I'm sorry she died.
我很难过
Did Dad say I get the dollhouse?
我有没有得到娃娃屋？
-You get the dollhouse. -I get the dollhouse!
你有 我得到娃娃屋了
A house for dolls! That is so cool.
娃娃住的屋子，好酷
When I was a kid,I had a barrel.
我小时候只有铁桶
You had a barrel for a dollhouse?
你拿铁桶当娃娃屋？
No,just a barrel.
不，就是一个铁桶
You know what? You can play with my dollhouse.
你可以玩我的娃娃屋
Really?
真的？
Any time you want.
随时欢迎
When I was young I wanted to play with this dollhouse.
我小的时候好想玩
But no! It was to be looked at, never played with.
但是不行，只准看、不准碰
My grandmother said the same thing to me.
我奶奶也是这样告戒我
The One With the Doll House
本集播出：“约会风波”
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
Thanks for lunch. You didn't have to walk me here.
谢谢你请我吃饭，还陪我回来
That's okay. No problem.
不客气
You realize we don't keep the women's lingerie here.
女性内衣不会放在办公室里
Yes,I realize that.
我知道
-Summer catalog. -That's the stuff.
夏季型录 就是这个
Rachel,I need the Versace invoice.
瑞秋，给我凡赛斯的发票
You don't work for me.
你不是我的员工
Joanna,this is my friend Chandler Bing. Joanna.
乔安娜，我的朋友钱德宾
Bing? That's a great name.
宾？很棒的姓
It's Gaelic for, "Thy turkey's done."
那是盖尔语的“火鸡煮好了”
-I'm gonna go. Nice meeting you. -You too.
我走了，幸会 彼此彼此
So what's wrong with him?
他怎么样？
Nothing. He's just goofy like that. I actually hardly notice it anymore.
他都这样疯疯癫癫的 我都没感觉了
I mean,is he married or involved with anyone?
我是说他已婚吗？有对象吗？
He's not married or involved with anyone.
不，他未婚，没有对象
Actually,you know what? Forget it.
我看还是算了
-I'll ask him for you,if you want. -Would you?
我可以帮你问他 真的？
Or is it too sad and desperate, like something Sophie would do?
会不会太可悲、太饥渴 就像苏菲会做的事？
-I am here. -I know that.
我在这里 我知道
Look at it!
你们看
Wallpaper's a little faded. That's okay.
壁纸有点褪色，没关系
Carpet's a little loose.
地毯有点翘起来
Hardwood floors?!
硬木地板？
-It's so beautiful! -I know!
好漂亮喔 我知道
So I'm here,ready to play!
我要来玩了
I brought a bunch of stuff for the house,so check it out.
我带了一堆东西来，看喔
What's this?
这是什么？
That's a dog. Every house should have a dog.
狗狗，每栋房子都应该有狗
Not one that can pee on the roof.
不能大到可以在屋顶上撒尿
Maybe it's so big because the house was built on radioactive waste.
也许是因为房子盖在 辐射废料掩埋地上
And is this in case the house sneezes?
这是房子打喷嚏用的？
No,that's the ghost for the attic.
不是，那是阁楼里的鬼
-I don't want a ghost. -Well,nobody wants a ghost.
我不要鬼 谁都不想闹鬼
But you've got one...
但是这里闹鬼
... because the house is sitting on an ancient lndian burial ground.
因为房子盖在印地安古坟场上
Wait a minute. The house was built on radioactive waste...
慢着，这栋房子盖在辐射废料
...and an ancient lndian burial ground?
和印地安古坟场上？
That would never happen.
那是不可能的
Obviously you don't know much about the U.S. government.
你太不了解美国政府了
-I need to talk to you. -Sure. What's up?
我有事找你 什么事？
Oh,sorry. I meant Chandler.
抱歉，我是说钱德
I know.
我知道
Well,if something comes up....
有事记得找我
I'm glad you guys are past that little awkward phase.
恭喜你们度过尴尬期
My boss. Joanna. When you left...
我的上司乔安娜，你一离开
...she started asking questions about you....
她就问起你的事…
Liked what she saw?
看上眼了？
Dug my action,did she?
喜欢我的表现？
Checking out the Chan Chan Man!
在探听小钱钱的事？
That was...
听起来…
...surreal.
怪怪的
What do you think? Are you interested?
怎样？有兴趣吗？
She seemed cool. Attractive. I'll do it.
她还不错，蛮漂亮的，好吧
Thank you,Chandler. This is great. She's gonna love me.
谢谢你，太好了，她会爱死我
Dinosaur attack! Quick,everybody into the house!
恐龙出击，大家快躲进屋里！
All right,Phoebe,you know what? That's it. That's it.
你知道吗？到此为止
No dinosaurs,no ghosts, no giant dogs,okay?
我不要恐龙、鬼 和超级大狗，好吗？
They're not the right size,they're not Victorian and they don't go.
比例不对，不是维多利亚风 一点也不相衬
Fine.
好
Come,dinosaur. We're not welcome in the house of no imagination.
恐龙，我们走 没有想像力的房子不欢迎我们
While we're on the subject, I have to say that dinosaurs...
趁这个机会，我想告诉你
...they don't go,"ruff!"
恐龙不会汪汪叫
The little ones do.
小恐龙会
“露西儿洛泰尔剧院”
-Hey,Kate. -Morning.
凯特 早
I went to that restaurant you talked about
我去了你说的那家餐厅…
Hey,lovely.
美女
Come,talk to me for a minute.
来跟我聊一下
I ate the food. It was good. I had the fish.
我在那里吃饭 很好吃，我点了鱼
I'm Lauren. Kate's understudy.
我是萝伦，凯特的候补
Joey Tribbiani.
乔伊崔比亚尼
I know.
我知道
I'm a big fan of yours.
我是你的超级影迷
What?
什么？
I used to schedule my classes so I could watch Dr. Drake Ramoray...
我以前经常翘课 好回家看“我们的岁月”
...on Days of our Lives.
和拉莫瑞医生
-Get out of here. Really? -Absolutely.
少来了，真的？ 真的
But then they dropped you down that elevator shaft.
结果他们让你掉到电梯井里
They gave me the shaft,all right.
他们是把我踢掉了
You're so funny.
你好幽默
What are you doing after rehearsal?
你排完戏要做什么？
You want to get a drink?
要不要去喝一杯？
Sure. A drink sounds great.
好啊，听起来不错
-Cool. I'll see you then. -All right.
酷，待会见 好
All right. It's time to act, my talking props.
该演戏了，会说话的道具们
Look everybody! Look at my new dollhouse!
你们看，我的新娃娃屋
Look,look!
你们看
Hey,what's this?
这是什么？
It's a slide instead of stairs. Look.
我用溜滑梯取代楼梯，看
Very interesting,Phoebe.
很有意思嘛
What's this?
这是什么？
The licorice room. You can eat all the furniture.
甘草房，砭愣伎梢猿
And when guests come over,they can stay on the Tootsie Roll-away bed.
客人来了可以睡在滑轮床上
This is the coolest house ever!
这栋房子有够酷的
Does anyone want to join me in the Aroma Room?
有人要跟我进芳香室吗？
-All right. -I would.
漂亮 我要
Hey,guys? Guys!
喂
Did you see my new china cabinet?
你们看到我的新瓷器柜了吗？
Watch. Watch.
看喔
And? And?
还有喔
Hey,my father's house does that.
我爸的房子也会那样
How did it go? Tell me everything!
怎么样？快说
The movie was great...
电影很好看
...dinner was great,and there's nothing like a cool,crisp New York evening.
晚餐很好吃 凉爽的纽约夜晚最宜人
Of course,I didn't enjoy any of that because Joanna's such a dull dud!
当然啦，我一点也不尽兴 因为乔安娜好无聊
Chandler is fantastic!
钱德太棒了
-What? -You know how people just click?
什么？ 你知道一拍即合吧？
He came by to pick me up,I opened the door and it was just like,"click!"
他来接我，我打开门 感觉一拍即合
Did he tell you?
他有告诉你吗？
Doesn't he have a good heart?
他的心肠很好吧？
And he's so sweet. He said he'd call,so put him straight through.
而且他好甜 他说他会打来，要立刻转给我
-lsn't this great? -Don't spoil it.
太好了 不要扫兴
Come on,baby,don't go. Please?
求求你，不要走
What do you say?
好吗？
It's you. Just one sec.
是你，等一下
I'm going to take this call.
我要接个电话
When I continue, I hope there will appear on-stage...
等我回来，希望台上会出现…
...this magical thing that in the theater we call...
一种神奇的东西 在剧场称之为…
...committing to the moment!
入戏！
The guy's like a cartoon.
他好可笑
What do you see in him,anyway?
你到底看上他哪一点？
He happens to be brilliant.
他很聪明
Which is more than I can say for that sweater you're dating.
比你那位毛衣女O好多了
I'm not interested in her sweater.
我不是看上她的毛衣
It's what's underneath her sweater that counts.
毛衣底下才重要
And besides...
而且…
...since when do you care who I'm with?
你几时开始关心我跟谁交往？
I don't care. Why,do you want me to care?
我才不关心，你希望我关心？
Do you want me to want you to care?
你希望我希望你关心吗？
Do you?
你呢？
What?
什么？
Okay. I'm afraid to say this, but let's pick up where we left off.
我实在很不想说 不过我们继续排吧
Come on,baby,don't go. Please? What do you say?
求求你，不要走 好吗？
I've got no reason to stay.
我没有理由要留下来
Stop!
停！
Stop it! You must stop!
停！别再演了
You are bad actors!
你们是烂演员
This is a terrible play!
这是出烂戏
I'll see you in the morning.
明天早上见
I can't believe we go on in a week.
居然一星期后就要上演了
Hey,it's gonna be all right.
没问题的
Since we're getting off early, do you want to go paint mugs?
既然提早收工 你想去画马克杯吗？
What?
什么？
At the place I told you about last night?
就是我昨晚说的那个地方
Yeah,with the mug-painting.
对了，那里可以画马克杯
I was so listening to that.
我听得很用心
But you know what? I need to work on my stuff tonight.
但是我今晚想好好练戏
I'll see you tomorrow.
那明天见
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
I guess.
还好吧
What are we gonna do about the scene?
这场戏怎么办？
I don't know.
不知道
Maybe if it had more heat.
也许应该再激烈一点
Well,how do you mean?
怎么说？
Adrianne's looking for a reason to stay,right?
爱莉安在寻找留下来的理由
Victor can't just kiss her. He's gotta...
维克不能只是亲她，他必须…
... he's gotta give her a reason.
必须给她有力的理由
Maybe he could slip her the tongue.
也许他可以对她舌吻
Or maybe...
或者…
... maybe he could grab her and lift her up.
他可以捉住她，把她抱起来
Then Adrianne could wrap her legs around his waist.
然后爱莉安用腿圈住他的腰
Then she could rip off his shirt and kiss his chest and stomach.
然后她扯开他的衣服 亲吻他的胸部、肚子
Then he could use his teeth to undo her dress and...
他可以用牙齿脱掉她的衣服
...and bite her!
然后咬她
Then right when the scene ends, he could take her...
在结尾的部份，他可以占有她
...with this raw,animal....
用他那原始的、兽性的…
Something like that?
像这样？
That's pretty much what I had in mind.
差不多
It's a little early to be drinking.
现在喝酒太早了吧
Things finally happened with Kate.
我跟凯特终于有进展了
You're kidding? That's great.
真的？太好了
It was so amazing.
感觉好棒
After the lovemaking...
做完爱之后…
Oh,my.
天哪
... I just watched her sleep for hours.
我看着她睡觉看了好久
Just breathing in...
就这样吸气…
...and breathing out.
吐气
I knew she was dreaming because...
我知道她在做梦，因为…
... her eyes kept going like this.
她的眼睛一直这样
I'm telling you, she's got it all wrong.
她完全误会了
All I said was,"This was fun. Let's do it again sometime.
我只是说 今晚很愉快，改天再聚
I'll give you a call."
我再打给你
I wonder why she thinks you're going to call her?
那她为什么觉得你会打给她？
It's what you say at the end of a date.
约完会都要这么说
You can't just say, "Nice to meet you. Good night?"
你就不能说 很高兴认识你，晚安？
To her face?
当着她的面？
I'm standing there...
一个晚上结束了
...she's waiting for me to say I'll call her...
我知道她在等我这句话
...and it comes out. I can't help it.
所以我就说了，我没办法
It's a compulsion.
我不由自主
When a guy says he'll call, it doesn't mean he's going to call.
男人说要联络也不见得会联络
This never happened to you?
你没碰过？
Well,they always called.
他们都会打给我
Bite me.
杀了我吧
-Did he call? -No,sorry.
他有打来吗？ 没有，对不起
Why? He said he'd call. Why hasn't he called?
为什么？他说要打来 怎么还不打来？
Maybe he's intimidated by smart, strong,successful women.
也许被你的美丽、成功吓到了
Sophie,will you please climb out of my butt.
苏菲，不要拍我的马屁
Why hasn't he called,Rachel? Why?
他为什么还不打来？
Maybe he feels awkward because you're my boss.
也许他会尴尬 因为你是我的上司
Awkward? Why should he feel awkward?
尴尬？为什么要尴尬？
You didn't tell him not to call me,did you?
你没叫他不要打给我吧？
If you're uncomfortable with your friend dating me...
要是你不喜欢你朋友跟我约会
...there are always ways to fix that.
我们可以想办法解决
Call her. Call her now!
现在就打给她
Multiple so many paper cuts.
我满手都被纸割伤了
"Why hasn't he called,Rachel? Why,why? I don't understand!"
他为什么还不打来？ 为什么？我不懂
I'm telling you,she's flipped out! She's gone crazy!
她很激动，她快疯了
Well,give me the phone then.
把电话拿来
She thinks it's my fault you haven't called her.
她觉得你不联络是我的错
You have to call her.
你一定要打给她
You can't call somebody after this long to say:
总不能过了这么久才打去说
"In case you didn't notice, I don't like you."
你或许没发现，我不喜欢你
Then you'll have to take her out again.
那就再带她出去一次
She's really dull, and she gets this...
不要，她很无聊，而且在眼角
...gross mascara-goop thing in the corner of her eye!
有一大块睫毛膏印子
I don't care!
我不管
You'll take her out again and end it...
你再约她一次，把话说清楚
...in a way she knows it's ended.
让她知道没希望
I don't care how hard it is. Don't tell her you'll call her again!
不管有多困难 千万别说你会再联络
All right,fine!
好
But just lunch. From now on,I get my own dates.
但只能吃午餐 以后我自己泡马子
I don't want you setting me up again!
你不要再帮我牵线了
That's fine!
没问题
-That's just a lot of big talk. -I know.
我只是说说 我知道
I'm in the shower!
我在洗澡
Fire! There's a fire! Fire!
失火了！失火了！
I talked to Lauren. I told her how things were with us.
我跟萝伦说了我们的事
Did you talk to Marshall?
你跟马歇尔说了吗？
About what?
说什么？
About what happened with us.
我们之间的事
No,there's really no reason why he should find out.
没有，他没有必要知道
So let's not make a big deal out of it,okay?
我们就别小题大作了
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
It was a big deal.
什么小题大作？
You can't tell me last night didn't mean something to you.
别说昨晚对你毫无意义
I was there. You're not that good an actress.
我也在，你没那么会演
I was just caught up in the moment.
我只是一时激情
That's all it was.
就这样
Joey,I'm sorry you feel bad,but...
抱歉让你觉得不好过
... haven't you slept with a woman and it meant more to her than to you?
你也曾经给别人这种感受吧？
Hi,pig!
王八蛋
Sorry I scared you in there.
抱歉吓到你了
It's okay.
没关系
By the way...
对了…
... I was just checking the shower massager.
我是在检查莲蓬头的功能
I tried to reach you at work.
我有打去公司找你
There's been a fire.
发生火灾了
What? Oh,my God!
什么？天哪！
What happened?
怎么了？
We believe it originated here...
我们相信起火点在这里
...in the Aroma Room.
就是芳香室
Did everyone get out okay?
大家都逃出来了吗？
The giraffe's okay, and so is the pirate.
长颈鹿没事，海盗也是
-What's this? -No,don't look!
这是什么？ 不要看
You don't want to see what's under there!
你不会想看的
The foster puppets!
领养的狗狗！
It's not a big deal. It's right here,and it's all the time.
其实没什么，就在这里 一直都在
Thanks again for lunch.
谢谢你这顿饭
-This was pleasant. -lt was,wasn't it?
很愉快 是吧？
-The food there was great. -Wasn't it?
那里的东西很好吃 是吧？
So take care.
保重
You too.
你也是
I'll give you a call. We should do it again!
我再打给你，改天再聚
Great. I'm looking forward to it.
太好了，我等你
-Any messages? -Sophie's desk.
有留言吗？ 在苏菲桌上
Are you gonna call her?
你会打给她吗？
I'm sorry,okay? I'm weak and pathetic and sorry.
我很抱歉好吗？ 我软弱、可悲又抱歉
You are gonna tell her. You'll tell her now.
你去告诉她，现在就说
I'm not gonna call you.
我不会打给你
What?
什么？
I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry I said I was going to when I'm not.
我不想打给你，却说要打给你
This has nothing to do with you.
跟你无关
And this isn't Rachel's fault. It's me.
也不是瑞秋的错，是我
I have serious problems when it comes to women.
我对女人有心理障碍
I have issues with commitment, intimacy...
我害怕承诺、害怕亲密
... mascara goop.
害怕睫毛膏印子
I'm really sorry. It's just that...
真的很抱歉，但是…
...this isn't going to work out.
我们之间是行不通的
This isn't how I was hoping this would end...
我没料到会有这种结局
... but I guess I have to appreciate your honesty.
但是我得谢谢你的诚实
I'll give you a call. We should do it again sometime!
我再打给你，改天再聚
Anyway,Beth, what I'm saying is...
贝丝，我想说的是
... I should have considered your feelings before I went home with you.
我跟你回家之前 应该先考虑你的心情
I've recently learned what it's like to be on your side...
我最近体会到你的感觉
...and I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
Do you think you can forgive me?
你可以原谅我吗？
Great. Thanks.
太好了，谢谢
Hello,Jennifer?
珍妮佛？
Hi,Mrs. Laurio. Is Jennifer there?
罗里欧太太，珍妮佛在吗？
She's not home,huh?
她不在？
Actually I kind of need to talk to you too.
事实上，我也要找你